The Jumbo Yearbook Records UA065
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Jumbo Yearbook Records
1952 -- 2005
2001 -- 2005
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Jumbo (Yearbook)
UA065
2.7 Linear Feet 6 boxes
1 Volumes
52 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection organized into four series: Senior portraits; Senior portraits and candid photographs; Special publications; and Senior candid photographs.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains original photographs used in the annual production of the Jumbo Book. For some years there are senior portraits only, and for others there are candid shots as well. It also includes a special centennial edition.
Related Materials
UP024, The Jumbo, DCA
Biographical / Historical
The Jumbo is the yearbook of the undergraduate colleges of Tufts University. It has been published annually since 1916, though the the title "The Jumbo" was first used for the 1917 edition. Over the years it has been known alternately as the Jumbo Book or simply Jumbo. In later years the yearbooks are often untitled.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Student life; Student Activities -- Student Publishing; Student life; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations
- Senior portraits, 2001; UA065.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains senior portraits of members of the Class of 2001.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Senior portraits, Aar-Alh, 2001; UA065.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, All-Bab, 2001; UA065.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Bag-Ber, 2001; UA065.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Ber-Bov, 2001; UA065.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Bow-Buc, 2001; UA065.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Bup-Cha, 2001; UA065.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Cha-Cri, 2001; UA065.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Chr-Coo, 2001; UA065.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Cup-Das, 2001; UA065.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Daw-Dim, 2001; UA065.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Dis-Dus, 2001; UA065.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Dym-Eng, 2001; UA065.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Eps-For, 2001; UA065.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, For-Gal, 2001; UA065.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Gal-Gla, 2001; UA065.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Gli-Gra, 2001; UA065.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Gra-Hal, 2001; UA065.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Hal-Her, 2001; UA065.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Her-Hor, 2001; UA065.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Hor-Jen, 2001; UA065.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Jes-Kee, 2001; UA065.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Kei-Kne, 2001; UA065.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Kni-Kuz, 2001; UA065.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, LaP-LeV, 2001; UA065.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Senior portraits, Lea-Lew, 2001; UA065.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Lew-Lut, 2001; UA065.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Lys-Mar, 2001; UA065.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Mar-McD, 2001; UA065.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, McE-Met, 2001; UA065.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Met-Mor, 2001; UA065.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Mor-Nap, 2001; UA065.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Nav-Ole, 2001; UA065.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Oli-Par, 2001; UA065.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Pat-Per, 2001; UA065.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Per-Pyl, 2001; UA065.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Qua-Ric, 2001; UA065.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Ric-Rot, 2001; UA065.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Rot-San, 2001; UA065.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Sar-Sch, 2001; UA065.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Sch-Sie, 2001; UA065.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Sik-Sow, 2001; UA065.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Spe-Ste, 2001; UA065.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Ste-Tav, 2001; UA065.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Taz-Tru, 2001; UA065.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Tun-Wal, 2001; UA065.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Wal-Wel, 2001; UA065.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Wex-Woo, 2001; UA065.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Senior portraits, Wal-Zyg, 2001; UA065.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
- Senior portraits and candids, 2003; UA065.002; 0.75 Linear Feet
  This series contains senior portraits of members of the Class of 2003. This series also contains candid photographs submitted by students for use in the yearbook. Photos that were used are grouped by page number. Photos that were not used are grouped at the end of the series.
  This series is arranged alphabetically and by page number.
  - Candids, pp. 2-5, 2003; UA065.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 8-15, 2003; UA065.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 23-27, 2003; UA065.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 29-33, 2003; UA065.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 40-45, 2003; UA065.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 46-55, 2003; UA065.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 53-59, 2003; UA065.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 62-116, 2003; UA065.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 116-140, 2003; UA065.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 142-145, 2003; UA065.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 145-150, 2003; UA065.002.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 150-151, 2003; UA065.002.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 151-153, 2003; UA065.002.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 153-155, 2003; UA065.002.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 155-157, 2003; UA065.002.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 157-159, 2003; UA065.002.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 159-161, 2003; UA065.002.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 162-164, 2003; UA065.002.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 164-167, 2003; UA065.002.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 1967-169, 2003; UA065.002.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Candids, p. 170, 2003; UA065.002.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 170-173, 2003; UA065.002.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 174-176, 2003; UA065.002.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 176-178, 2003; UA065.002.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 178-179, 2003; UA065.002.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Candids, p. 179, 2003; UA065.002.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 180-182, 2003; UA065.002.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 182-183, 2003; UA065.002.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 183-185, 2003; UA065.002.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 185-187, 2003; UA065.002.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 187-188, 2003; UA065.002.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 189-198, 2003; UA065.002.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 190-192, 2003; UA065.002.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 192-193, 2003; UA065.002.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 193-194, 2003; UA065.002.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 194-195, 2003; UA065.002.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 195-198, 2003; UA065.002.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 198-204, 2003; UA065.002.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 205-209, 2003; UA065.002.003.00039 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 209-212, 2003; UA065.002.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 214-235, 2003; UA065.002.003.00041 (Box 3)
  - Candids, pp. 236-262, 2003; UA065.002.003.00042 (Box 3)
  - Unpublished candids, athletics: baseball, basketball, track, 2003; UA065.002.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, athletics: sailing, crew, tennis, soccer, 2003; UA065.002.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, athletics, football, 2003; UA065.002.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, athletics, football, 2003; UA065.002.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, athletics, football, 2003; UA065.002.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, band, 2003; UA065.002.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, cheerleading, 2003; UA065.002.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, cheerleading, 2003; UA065.002.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, Homecoming Coronation, 2003; UA065.002.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, Homecoming Parade, 2003; UA065.002.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, Homecoming Parade, 2003; UA065.002.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, Homecoming tailgate party, 2003; UA065.002.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, people and parties, 2003; UA065.002.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, people and parties, 2003; UA065.002.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, student groups, 2003; UA065.002.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, student groups, 2003; UA065.002.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, student groups, 2003; UA065.002.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, student groups, 2003; UA065.002.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, student groups, 2003; UA065.002.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, student groups, 2003; UA065.002.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, student groups, 2003; UA065.002.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Unpublished candids, student groups, 2003; UA065.002.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Senior Portraits, Ki-Kr, 2003; UA065.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Senior Portraits, Mu-Ra, 2003; UA065.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Senior Portraits, Re-Sc, 2003; UA065.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Senior Portraits, Se-Sw, 2003; UA065.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Senior Portraits, Sy-Zo, 2003; UA065.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Ballou Hall, p. 8, 2003; UA065.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
- Special publications, 1952; UA065.003; 1 Volumes; 52 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains the Centennial History of Tufts College, published by the Jumbo Book in 1952 as a supplement to that year's yearbook.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Tufts College: A Centennial History, 1952; UA065.003.006.00001 (Box Volume 6)
    Additional copies in the Reading Room.
    - Hannah Tufts, UA065.003.006.00001.00001; Unknown
      Illustration from Tufts College: A Centennial History.
      Tufts, Hannah Robinson
    - Charles Tufts, UA065.003.006.00001.00002; Unknown
      Tufts, Charles
    - Festival celebration for the opening of Tufts College, UA065.003.006.00001.00003; Unknown
      Tufts College
    - 'Gem of the Ocean', UA065.003.006.00001.00004; Unknown
      Ships
    - Alumni Day baseball game, 1920, UA065.003.006.00001.00005; Unknown
      Illustration from Tufts College: A Centennial History. This date is approximate.
    - Approach to the Hill, 1892, UA065.003.006.00001.00006; Unknown
      Paintings; Views
    - Hosea Ballou 2nd, 1892, UA065.003.006.00001.00007; Unknown
      Paintings; Portraits; People; Ballou, Hosea, 2d
    - Royall House, Medford, UA065.003.006.00001.00008; Unknown
      Buildings; Houses
    - View of Tufts College during the Civil War, UA065.003.006.00001.00009; Unknown
      Buildings; Views; Paintings
    - Student group at Tufts seventy years ago., UA065.003.006.00001.00010; Unknown
      Student activities; Students
    - No. 8 West Hall seventy years ago, 1880, UA065.003.006.00001.00011; Unknown
      Furniture; Building sites; Interior views
    - West Hall eighty years ago, 1870, UA065.003.006.00001.00012; Unknown
      People; Building sites; Trees
    - Quadrangle before the campus fence was built, UA065.003.006.00001.00013; Unknown
    - Tufts sailboats on the Mystic Lakes, near present Collge Yacht Club House, UA065.003.006.00001.00016; Unknown
      Water; Boats; Sailing
    - Site of present Cousens Gymnasium showing Major Stearns' mansion in the foreground, UA065.003.006.00001.00017; Unknown
      Buildings; Trees; Bird's-eye views
    - Alonzo Ames Miner, president, UA065.003.006.00001.00018; Unknown
      People; Miner, Alonzo Ames
    - Elmer Hewitt Capen, class of 1860, third president, UA065.003.006.00001.00019; Unknown
      People; Capen, Elmer Hewitt
    - Frederick William Hamilton, president, UA065.003.006.00001.00020; Unknown
      People; Hamilton, Frederick William
    - Herman Carey Bumpus, president, UA065.003.006.00001.00022; Unknown
      People; Bumpus, Hermon Carey
    - George Stewart Miller, acting president, 1937 -- 1938, UA065.003.006.00001.00024; Unknown
      People; Miller, George Stewart
    - Old College Hill Railroad Station site now occupied by Tufts College Press, UA065.003.006.00001.00025; Unknown
      Railroad stations
    - Sketch of Tufts College thirty years ago, 1922, UA065.003.006.00001.00026; Unknown
      Tufts University -- History
    - Old College reservoir showing reflections of gatehoust, radio mast, and West Hall, UA065.003.006.00001.00030; Unknown
      Buildings; Reservoirs; Water
    - Interior - old chemistry laboratory, UA065.003.006.00001.00031; Unknown
      Buildings; Interior views; Lamps (lighting devices)
    - Class Day of yore, UA065.003.006.00001.00032; Unknown
      People; Processions
    - Barnum biology and geology building before modern additions, UA065.003.006.00001.00034; Unknown
      Building sites; Trees
    - Early engineering laboratory, UA065.003.006.00001.00035; Unknown
      Laboratories
    - Interior - Bray Mechanical Engineering Laboratory, UA065.003.006.00001.00036; Unknown
      Laboratories; Interior views
    - Exterior of one of the modern engineering laboratories at Tufts, UA065.003.006.00001.00037; Unknown
      Laboratories; Building sites; Exterior views
    - Early electrical laboratory, UA065.003.006.00001.00038; Unknown
      Laboratories; Building sites; Interior views
    - Students testing equipment in Electrical Engineering Laboratory, UA065.003.006.00001.00039; Unknown
      Laboratories; Building sites; Interior views; Students
    - An early radio broadcast from Tufts showing Professors I. Andrews, H. Rockwell, and H. Gilmer.Dean G. C. Anthony is at the microphone., UA065.003.006.00001.00040; Unknown
      Building sites; Interior views; Students; Professors
    - Stephen M. Babcock, '66, in his laboratory at Wisconsin, UA065.003.006.00001.00041; Unknown
      Professors; People; Babcock, Stephen
    - Austin B. Fletcher, '76, Tufts' largest donor, UA065.003.006.00001.00044; Unknown
      People; Fletcher, Austin Barclay
    - Henry J. Braker, generous Tufts donor, UA065.003.006.00001.00045; Unknown
      People; Braker, Henry Jones
    - Part of Reading Room - Fletcher Library, UA065.003.006.00001.00046; Unknown
      Rooms; Furniture; Lamps (lighting devices)
    - Mt. Fay, named for C. E. Fay, '68, on Continental Divide in Canadian Rockies, UA065.003.006.00001.00047; Unknown
      Mountains; Snow
    - Charles Ernest Fay, '68, Professor of Modern Languages and mountainee, UA065.003.006.00001.00048; Unknown
      People; Fay, Charles Ernest
    - Interior - Crane Chapel, UA065.003.006.00001.00049; Unknown
      Interior views; Chapels
    - Princess Ida, an operetta of the early days, UA065.003.006.00001.00050; Unknown
      Theater
    - Jumbo in his new home, UA065.003.006.00001.00051; Unknown
      People; Students
    - Dr. Leo Lewis, UA065.003.006.00001.00052; Unknown
      People; Lewis, Leo R.
    - An early Tufts Glee Club, UA065.003.006.00001.00053; Unknown
      People; Students; Music and musical performances
    - Bowen Gate and Goddard Chapel tower, UA065.003.006.00001.00055; Unknown
      Chapels; Building sites
    - The old college willows - road to Medford Square past present Cousens Gymnasium site, UA065.003.006.00001.00056; Unknown
      Roads; Trees; Gates
    - The old Medical and Dental Building on Huntington Ave., UA065.003.006.00001.00058; Unknown
      Building sites
    - An Anatomy Lab of the New Medical School, UA065.003.006.00001.00059; Unknown
      Building sites; Interior views
    - The present Tufts Medical School, UA065.003.006.00001.00060; Unknown
      Building sites; Exterior views
    - A corner of Hamilton Memorial Swimming Pool, UA065.003.006.00001.00061; Unknown
      Interior views; Swimming
    - Navy ROTC on parade, UA065.003.006.00001.00062; Unknown
      NROTC; Processions; Parades; Students
    - S. S. Charles Tufts, launched Oct. 10, UA065.003.006.00001.00063; Unknown
      Ships; People; Scaffolds; Flags; Tufts, Charles
    - Skiing on the campus, UA065.003.006.00001.00064; Unknown
      Skiing; Trees; Snow
- Senior yearbook candids, 2004 -- 2005; UA065.004; 0.25 Linear Feet
  This series contains candid shots from the classes of 2004 and 2005. The candid photographs were submitted by students for use in the yearbook. Those in the collection may have been used in the yearbook, but were not picked up by students at the end of the year. They are unorganized.
  This series is not arranged.
  - Senior Candids, 2004; UA065.004.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Senior Candids, 2005; UA065.004.001.00002 (Box 1)
    Many of these images are of Campus organizations.